<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on </title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>A Shitass Life</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitasslife/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitasslife/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;facist-shitass-cowards&#34;&gt;Facist Shitass Cowards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Led by &amp;ldquo;Little Big&amp;rdquo; Bovino, Company Man, the Christian Nationalists Thug; The modern iteration of ICE and CBP are insane.
:customs: :passpost-control:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;quite-obviously-insane&#34;&gt;Quite obviously insane.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;who-the-fuck-poses-for-a-picture-like-this&#34;&gt;Who the fuck poses for a picture like this?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;figure class=&#34;ma0 w-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/static/bigDick.jpg&#34;
    alt=&#34;The Roaming Asshat in Charge&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Bovino is reported to be the guy who tells everyone to be scared. He then lets you know, he&amp;rsquo;s the only one that can save you.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-runt-got-moved-because-he-lies-like-a-rug&#34;&gt;The Runt got moved, because he lies like a rug.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too bad he&amp;rsquo;ll likely get to keep pension and get qualified immunity for attempted cover up of blatant homicide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="facist-shitass-cowards">Facist Shitass Cowards</h2>
<p>Led by &ldquo;Little Big&rdquo; Bovino, Company Man, the Christian Nationalists Thug; The modern iteration of ICE and CBP are insane.
:customs: :passpost-control:</p>
<h3 id="quite-obviously-insane">Quite obviously insane.</h3>
<h3 id="who-the-fuck-poses-for-a-picture-like-this">Who the fuck poses for a picture like this?</h3>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/bigDick.jpg"
    alt="The Roaming Asshat in Charge"><figcaption>
      <p>Bovino is reported to be the guy who tells everyone to be scared. He then lets you know, he&rsquo;s the only one that can save you.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<h2 id="the-runt-got-moved-because-he-lies-like-a-rug">The Runt got moved, because he lies like a rug.</h2>
<p>Too bad he&rsquo;ll likely get to keep pension and get qualified immunity for attempted cover up of blatant homicide.</p>
<p>Cos-play doesn&rsquo;t fucking cut it. The social network aspect aside, the out in the open fear-mongering via military style kit (tacti-cool!) is about as unserious and pathetic as it gets. It&rsquo;s straight up make-believe to wear military style bullshit inside the United States and it&rsquo;s not, a fucking war.</p>
<h2 id="we-all-knew-bovino-is-a-real-see-ya-next-tuesday-sort">We all knew Bovino is a real, see ya next tuesday sort.</h2>
<p>Always with the, &ldquo;You aren&rsquo;t safe&rdquo; horseshit. Rapidly and weirdly mouthed follow up of, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m the only one who can protect you!&rdquo;</p>
<p>The public backlash causing the Runt to flee, is going to push their stupid money wasting agenda to the down-low (as much as the possibly can). Hopefully, we can keep eyes on it.</p>
<p>You can run on for a long time&hellip; (RIP Mr. Cash)</p>
<p>Yeah, you can <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IStlBOX9F4o">run on</a> for a long time, no matter what you believe, it all comes out in the open. That&rsquo;s god/the-universe, cutting you down.</p>
<p>Aloha nui loa.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>About This Site</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;surrounded-by-shitasses&#34;&gt;Surrounded by Shitasses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class=&#34;ma0 w-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/static/tommyToiletSez.jpg&#34;
    alt=&#34;Don&amp;#39;t be a Shitass&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t be like Donald Trump, who reportedly reeks all day.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wife over here, her grandma (who was married to a veteran of Okinawa, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/96th_Infantry_Division_%28United_States%29&#34;&gt;Deadeye&lt;/a&gt; of the 96th) had a term for the likes that brought instant and likely intense displeasure to her mind. A Shitass, quite plainly. A non-wiping fuckwit who cannot get out of their own way, is how I see it. Wife just responded, &amp;ldquo;yeah&amp;rdquo; to my query on if her grandma would have agreed w/ my assessment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="surrounded-by-shitasses">Surrounded by Shitasses</h2>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/tommyToiletSez.jpg"
    alt="Don&#39;t be a Shitass"><figcaption>
      <p>Don&rsquo;t be like Donald Trump, who reportedly reeks all day.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The wife over here, her grandma (who was married to a veteran of Okinawa, a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/96th_Infantry_Division_%28United_States%29">Deadeye</a> of the 96th) had a term for the likes that brought instant and likely intense displeasure to her mind. A Shitass, quite plainly. A non-wiping fuckwit who cannot get out of their own way, is how I see it. Wife just responded, &ldquo;yeah&rdquo; to my query on if her grandma would have agreed w/ my assessment.</p>
<p>So anyway, because I have the bandwidth and ability, the spirit of my parents and grandparents animating me, I had to build this site. Our veep, the Thiel acolyte, JD Vance, told folks to write an essay instead of protesting. Well, OK JD, you mighty-personality-morphing power ranger. Here it is, now suck my dick, from the back. That JD has been led to water by Thiel, should be a definate pause for concern. Shit though, I&rsquo;m seguing like a wide bus down a narrow street.</p>
<h3 id="i-hate-to-think">I hate to think&hellip;</h3>
<h4 id="what-would-her-grandpa-have-thought-about-people-wrapping-themselves-in-words-of-freedom-and-love-then-doing-the-exact-opposite-to-the-nation-that-is-supposed-to-be-governed-by-them">What would her grandpa have thought about people wrapping themselves in words of freedom and love, then doing the exact opposite to the nation that is supposed to be governed by them?</h4>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/ibiblio-hyperwar-maps-okinawa-35.jpg"
    alt="The Maedea Escarpment map, when Wife&#39;s grandpa visited."><figcaption>
      <p>Not a fun time, by any account I have read, and Wife&rsquo;s grandpa didn&rsquo;t say shit about what it was really like, to the women in their family. Wife&rsquo;s uncle is a &lsquo;Nam vet, even he couldn&rsquo;t comprehend the death machine his dad had gotten sent into&hellip; And her Uncle saw &rsquo;the shit&rsquo; as a damn convoy gunner in the late 1960&rsquo;s, had intimate knowledge of immediate and personal danger to oneself. Yeah, Wife&rsquo;s grandpa wouldn&rsquo;t be impressed at all, with this authoritarian worshipping lot. The asshats in charge like to take a bunch of &lsquo;Christian Nation under God&rsquo; gibberish, but it&rsquo;s all it is. A giant wooden nickle people, ain&rsquo;t worth a damn.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<h2 id="we-value-approaching-life-without-side-stepping-responsibility">We value approaching life without side-stepping responsibility.</h2>
<h4 id="kuleanapersonal-responsibility-is-the-core-of-our-existence-to-turn-away-from-it-is-to-relinquish-ones-soul">Kuleana/Personal Responsibility is the core of our existence. To turn away from it, is to relinquish ones soul.</h4>
<h5 id="operating-from-love-as-opposed-to-fear-is-true-courage">Operating from love as opposed to fear, is true courage.</h5>
<p>To qualify ourselves as flawed, decent, humans;</p>
<p>So yeah, I believe in community and truth. Wife, she was always a straight-shooter, still is. We both believe that love is a better tool and frame of mind, than fear.</p>
<p>We do our utmost to remember that, denial isn&rsquo;t just a river in Egypt. If it sounds to good to be true, it is. Finally, my favorite; Technology isn&rsquo;t going to fix anything technology has broken.</p>
<p>Aloha nui loa.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Shitass of the Week</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitassoftheweek/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitassoftheweek/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-shitass-parade&#34;&gt;The Shitass Parade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Week of Jan 25th - 31st:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ICE Barbie.
K. Noem is seemingly, a horrid person. She is a blatant liar, on air, for all to witness.
Hides behind god? Check!
Knows absolutely nothing about the law? Check!
Will do anything for Donald Trump that serves her greed? Check!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;cos-play-time-anyone&#34;&gt;Cos-Play Time Anyone?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;figure class=&#34;ma0 w-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/static/iceBarbie.jpg&#34;
    alt=&#34;ICE Barbie Queen&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Noem and Lewandowski sitting in a sty. Corey blew his wad, into Kristy&amp;rsquo;s eye. She threw a fucking fit, and ran away, but Corey really runs the show on the day to day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-shitass-parade">The Shitass Parade</h2>
<p>Week of Jan 25th - 31st:</p>
<p>ICE Barbie.
K. Noem is seemingly, a horrid person. She is a blatant liar, on air, for all to witness.
Hides behind god? Check!
Knows absolutely nothing about the law? Check!
Will do anything for Donald Trump that serves her greed? Check!</p>
<h4 id="cos-play-time-anyone">Cos-Play Time Anyone?</h4>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/iceBarbie.jpg"
    alt="ICE Barbie Queen"><figcaption>
      <p>Noem and Lewandowski sitting in a sty. Corey blew his wad, into Kristy&rsquo;s eye. She threw a fucking fit, and ran away, but Corey really runs the show on the day to day.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Yeah, that&rsquo;s one real winner.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>WTF Over?</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wtfover/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wtfover/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-internet-has-not-been-your-friend&#34;&gt;The Internet, has not Been Your Friend.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here we are. Take a look around, it appears sorta sketchy and not friendly right now. The disinformation onion that is the Internet, has fucked the United States up, flatter than a hammered cock. How useful is a hammered cock people?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is it we always want to believe the worst about one another, without really looking at ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m left with assumptions, can&amp;rsquo;t answer the above other than to hazard, we forget to act and think from a place of love. The universe for humans, is governed by fear and love. We have to choose daily, how we are going to approach the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-internet-has-not-been-your-friend">The Internet, has not Been Your Friend.</h2>
<p>But here we are. Take a look around, it appears sorta sketchy and not friendly right now. The disinformation onion that is the Internet, has fucked the United States up, flatter than a hammered cock. How useful is a hammered cock people?</p>
<p>Why is it we always want to believe the worst about one another, without really looking at ourselves?</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m left with assumptions, can&rsquo;t answer the above other than to hazard, we forget to act and think from a place of love. The universe for humans, is governed by fear and love. We have to choose daily, how we are going to approach the world.</p>
<h2 id="flat-earth-and-q-critical-thinking-remains-deeply-unpopular">Flat Earth and Q; Critical Thinking Remains Deeply Unpopular.</h2>
<p>Before the prominance in our lives of the Internet, both Flat Earth and Q proponents would have been committed to an asylum or learned to keep shit on the down low.</p>
<p>The American penchant for contrarianism and anti-intellectualism has now been given the biggest microphone ever. That the Earth can be proven a globe is no matter to people who have decided, they know the truth bc of secret sources that, &rsquo;the they&rsquo;s&rsquo; don&rsquo;t want us to know about.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s ok that some people are smarter (or faster, stronger, Etc&hellip;) than us. Yo! It all leavens out. It does suck that things like, &ldquo;Nicotene has been shown to cause cancer.&rdquo; But it took smart people to figure it out for the rest of us, corporations were just going to keep taking adavntage of human addictive behavior and kill us early to make a buck.</p>
<p>Conversley though, smart motherfuckers shouldn&rsquo;t be just thinking all the rest of us are stupid. Again, it all leavens out and truely, we&rsquo;re all in it together.</p>
<h2 id="step-3-change">Step 3. Change.</h2>
<p>Sometimes, some change is needed, so things can run better. Change is required on all sides of the coin. Neither political party is worth a wet cotton sock in a snowstorm, as both are locked in thrall to corporate money and social networking likes.</p>
<p>There is a huge amount of money arrayed against meaningful change. In my opinion, unlimited money. The rich have decided were going back to the 1800&rsquo;s style of global carve up. What can I say about that other than, greed blinds folks from historical facts. I guess that when yer rich as Midas, you begin to believe that, you aren&rsquo;t subject to the same mistakes others have made before. Drunks call it, ten foot tall &rsquo;n bulletproof. Some philosophers would call it, an egoic lack of self honesty. I call it, morons with money.</p>
<p>We have to practice and get better at not taking their money for inaction. If anything, heh. We need to fool them into funding our action to corral their power and ability to wreak havoc on our lives.</p>
<h2 id="step-4-having-and-being-a-better-nation">Step 4. Having and being a better nation.</h2>
<p>Isn&rsquo;t having and holding something that lives up to the founding documents of the United States of America a worthy &rsquo;thinig&rsquo; in and of itself? I believe myself to be deeply American and was raised with the values of my Grandparents. The generation who so many look to through a nostolgic haze, the folks who held it down throughout the scrap w/ Imperial Japan and the Third Reich. What&rsquo;s funny is the grandparents who raised me, could look candidly at the past they had survived and agree that, &ldquo;The only good thing about the good old days is that they are gone.&rdquo; I mean it quite literally as well, they survived.
He (and a few hundred other souls) had a ship blown out from under him and sunk sitting at Lunga Roads, Ironbottom Sound, Solomon Islands. Then, after he and other shipless lads, formed Advanced Naval Base parties, to man the forward bases built by CB&rsquo;s. On Vella Lavella, while attempting to save some lads from NZ, he picked up a Silver Star and his second Purple Heart (single star).
She got Tuberculosis when my ma was a kid. Was put into a sanitarium w/ the other &rsquo;lungers&rsquo; (she told me that when I was 7, to my horror), so that he and my ma would go see her on weekends. For six months. They were tough as nails just because they had to be, when it was needed.
My dad&rsquo;s parents were slightly more conservative, but cast from the same mold of needing to be tough because of the times.</p>
<p>Not going to varnish over things, both sets of grandparents had some (to me, as a kid), astonishing racial views. That said however, they all were willing to modify beliefs as they got older. Not out of fear either, they all trusted people like my ma, who in a lot of ways, was a very progressive type, and introduced them to different people of different backgrounds.</p>
<p>The biggest catch to it all, those crafty grandparents of mine. They really meant it when they told me, &ldquo;It matters not what color, creed or original nationality. When someone is here and a, law-abiding, participating member of American society, they are welcome to the club.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 id="so">So.</h2>
<h3 id="go-fuck-yerself-stephen-miller-and-fuck-project2025-26">Go fuck yerself Stephen Miller, and fuck Project2025-26.</h3>
<p>Vought and Miller, sitting in a tree. One tried to screw, the crease in the others knee. First came hate, then came marraige, they push Trump around in a baby carraige.</p>
<p>Hideous rhymes aside, were in a pickle. The &rsquo;elites&rsquo; are seemingly trying to lock dissent out via their tools in D.C. and at the regional level. But it&rsquo;s financial as well. The push for the U.S. stablecoin looks to be enmeshed w/ the Trump family in too many ways to be good for anyone else. The family&rsquo;s past is the record to go off of, and it&rsquo;s corrupt. Seemingly, nothing they do is above board.</p>
<p>Note, not grandparent condoned language, but they&rsquo;d get it at this point in time. I knew them well enough, as they lived long lives and were in their late 40&rsquo;s when I was born. They hooked me up w/ some choice vocab. One of the sayings I&rsquo;m remembering most right now is; &ldquo;The fix is in.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Back with more scuttlebutt later on!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
