<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on </title>
        <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://shitass.life/home/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>A Shitass Life</title>
            <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitasslife/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitasslife/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;murder-crew&#34;&gt;Murder Crew&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ice-bortac-the-government-murders-alex-pretti-from-behind-while-he-is-on-hands-and-knees&#34;&gt;ICE? BORTAC?, The Government murders Alex Pretti, from behind, while he is on hands and knees.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;ma0 w-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://shitass.life/home/static/ice-kills.jpg&#34;
    alt=&#34;The Murder Crew&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;RIP Alex Pretti.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

UPDATE: &lt;strong&gt;The Runt&lt;/strong&gt;  got moved, because he lies like a goddamned rug.
Too bad he&amp;rsquo;ll likely get to keep pension and get qualified immunity for attempted cover up of Pretti&amp;rsquo;s murder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-all-knew-bovino-is-a-real-cee-u-next-tuesday-sort&#34;&gt;We all knew Bovino is a real, cee u next tuesday, sort.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s lying to cover murder up, for The Runt?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="murder-crew">Murder Crew</h2>
<h3 id="ice-bortac-the-government-murders-alex-pretti-from-behind-while-he-is-on-hands-and-knees">ICE? BORTAC?, The Government murders Alex Pretti, from behind, while he is on hands and knees.</h3>
<p><figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/ice-kills.jpg"
    alt="The Murder Crew"><figcaption>
      <p>RIP Alex Pretti.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

UPDATE: <strong>The Runt</strong>  got moved, because he lies like a goddamned rug.
Too bad he&rsquo;ll likely get to keep pension and get qualified immunity for attempted cover up of Pretti&rsquo;s murder.</p>
<h2 id="we-all-knew-bovino-is-a-real-cee-u-next-tuesday-sort">We all knew Bovino is a real, cee u next tuesday, sort.</h2>
<p>What&rsquo;s lying to cover murder up, for The Runt?</p>
<p>The public backlash causing The &lsquo;ol Runt-o-rooni to flee? I don&rsquo;t think it&rsquo;ll impact the administration&rsquo;s <strong>&ldquo;Fear of the Other Tour, 2026&rdquo;</strong>. Stephen Miller is some kinda far-out goddamned ghoul who thrives on this shit. His strident, freakish yammering about white replacement due to liberalism? It&rsquo;s completely inline with the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stab-in-the-back_myth">&ldquo;November Criminals&rdquo;</a> horseshit a certain wretched Austrian corporal latched onto all those years ago.</p>
<p>Cowards can <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IStlBOX9F4o">run on</a> for a long time, but it all comes out in the open.</p>
<p>I hope the the <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2026/jan/28/deaths-ice-2026-">eight people</a> who have died in 2026, in the name of stopping &ldquo;white replacement&rdquo;, are the last. Doesn&rsquo;t life matter to us?</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sacrifice</title>
            <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/sacrifice/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://shitass.life/home/posts/sacrifice/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;those-who-came-before-me&#34;&gt;Those Who Came Before Me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;its-a-free-country-if-you-have-money-is-what-my-grandfather-told-me-once&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a free country, if you have money.&amp;rdquo; Is what my grandfather told me once.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heh, didn&amp;rsquo;t stick in like it should. I have a mouth though, and can flap the shit outta my gums. I can&amp;rsquo;t really write all to well, but ability hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped me yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My grandfather served in the USNR during WW2. He (and a whole buncha other coxwains) landed troops in N. Africa, 8 November 1942. Once the landing were done, the ship he was on (USS John Penn), headed to Norfolk, VA. By 17 Dec, 1942, they were headed to the Canal Zone and onto New Caledonia in the Pacific Theatre. The ship sailed in hotly contested waters until August 1943. She arrived at Guadalcanal and anchored at Lunga Roads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="those-who-came-before-me">Those Who Came Before Me</h2>
<h3 id="its-a-free-country-if-you-have-money-is-what-my-grandfather-told-me-once">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s a free country, if you have money.&rdquo; Is what my grandfather told me once.</h3>
<p>Heh, didn&rsquo;t stick in like it should. I have a mouth though, and can flap the shit outta my gums. I can&rsquo;t really write all to well, but ability hasn&rsquo;t stopped me yet.</p>
<p>My grandfather served in the USNR during WW2. He (and a whole buncha other coxwains) landed troops in N. Africa, 8 November 1942. Once the landing were done, the ship he was on (USS John Penn), headed to Norfolk, VA. By 17 Dec, 1942, they were headed to the Canal Zone and onto New Caledonia in the Pacific Theatre. The ship sailed in hotly contested waters until August 1943. She arrived at Guadalcanal and anchored at Lunga Roads.</p>
<p>The USS John Penn (APA 23) was attacked by IJN B5N&rsquo;s (&ldquo;Kate&rdquo;) and while fighting them off, one of the planes got hit, went out of control and hit the Penn in the mainmast area. Right around the same instant, another Kate&rsquo;s torpedo hit her on the starboard side. She sank in about 130&rsquo; of water.</p>
<p>My grandfather, was blown into a bulkhead and then launched overboard with all the blast concussion and violent lifting of the ship. He didn&rsquo;t remember hitting water but woke up soon after (his account). He doesn&rsquo;t remember getting fished out, but remembered the boat pulling up to pier and the marines helping them into the arms of corpmen.</p>
<p>He ended up getting the shit shot out of him, running an LCVP into an extermely narrow (read enfilading) bay in the dead hours of the early morning, Solomon Islands, Vella Lavella, early October, 1944. He, his crew and a half dozen New Zealanders, were going to attempt to get NewZealanders, at the head of the bay, out of the tight squeeze their battalion found itself in.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve since learned more, but that&rsquo;s all grampa ever told me. It turned FUBAR fast and he was lucky to make it home. he never once displayed the medals or the souviners he brought back. He knew young men are fooled by medals and trinkets from wars in far away places, why glorify having to put other humans in the ground?</p>
<p>He raised me to always be skeptical of what politicians promised. At the end of it all, he watched the nation go through the most unreal growth ever, then begin to drastically decline, especially with regards to how citizenry are taxed. The carve outs for rich now are obscene, I&rsquo;ll save that for another posting.</p>
<p>He&rsquo;d of had to have fought nausea off w/ regards to the current crew that runs our shitass life here in the U.S.A. If a German newspaper is thinking G. Bovino looks like an Ernst Rohem wannabe, my grandpa&rsquo;s crew would be puking.</p>
<h3 id="i-hate-to-think">I hate to think&hellip;</h3>
<p>What would wife&rsquo;s grandpa have thought about folks wrapping themselves in the flag and spounting words of freedom and patriotism, then performing actions designed to have the opposite effect on this nation. The home that he&rsquo;d gone off to fight the IJN for. He got the shit shot out of him in the Phillipines and healed up, then went to Okinawa and had it done to him again. Because the nation asked him, he went and did it. It was a nation worth fighting for then. Look where greed has gotten us. Below is a map of some of the ground Wife&rsquo;s grandpa and his buddies in the 96th got intimate with. If you know about Okinawa, you know.</p>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/ibiblio-hyperwar-maps-okinawa-35.jpg"
    alt="The Maedea Escarpment map, when Wife&#39;s grandpa visited."><figcaption>
      <p>I&rsquo;ve read about this part of that battle a few times now and am astounded that anyone made it at all. Of note, Mr. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Desmond_Doss">Desmond Doss</a> was considered not only a hero, but a good luck charm, by the men who served closely with him at the Maedea Escarpment. A class act of a human being and a fine American, who wouldn&rsquo;t willingly touch a firearm. Wife&rsquo;s grandpa&rsquo;s company (G Co., 381st, 96th) hit the top of the ridge, eighteen casualties were sustained in a matter of minutes. <a href="https://www.ibiblio.org/hyperwar/USA/USA-P-Okinawa/USA-P-Okinawa-11.html">US vs. Empire of Japan, Okinawa</a></p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<h2 id="we-wife-n-i-were-raised-by-and-around-good-men-gentle-and-kind-men">We (Wife &rsquo;n I) were raised by and around good men. Gentle and kind men.</h2>
<p>Men who had been asked to risk it all in hot, malaria infested environments that every once and awhile, had what the German&rsquo;s called, <em><strong>&ldquo;Steel Weather&rdquo;</strong></em>. Men who considered themselves Christian, but didn&rsquo;t overdo it, leaving church for the wives and just hitting the Christmas and Easter magic shows.
There wasn&rsquo;t frothing anti-immigrant fear and hate. Wife&rsquo;s family goes back further here in the U.S., but hell&hellip; My grandpa was second generation. His grandparents (Catholic grandpa, Jewish grandma) bailed on Europe because of inflexible intolerance and never ending wars.
We are all immigrants, even the original colonists. Hell, go back far enough, it&rsquo;s just the story of us (humanity). Long term, mass immigration, to find a better place to live.</p>
<h2 id="now-w-agent-orange-v2">Now w/ Agent Orange v.2</h2>
<p>The fix is in. Greed is good and lets burn the joint down so Elon Musk, Peter Thiel, Sergey Brin, Larry Page and the rest of the morons with money can take it over and screw us forever.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Shitasses Serving Shit Sandwiches</title>
            <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitasses/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitasses/</guid>
            <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;ma0 w-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://shitass.life/home/static/bovino-heil.jpg&#34;
    alt=&#34;Big Facist, Little Greg&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of Bovino letting the folks of Chicago know he&amp;rsquo;s on top of being a Facist dick.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;governmental-breakdown&#34;&gt;Governmental Breakdown&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What has transpired since Agent Orange took office for a second time, is pretty phenominal. Not in a good way for the rank and file here in the U.S. More of a, societal upheaval as the rich get on with betraying the nation that allowed them to amass the fortunes they&amp;rsquo;ve aquired and stashed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/bovino-heil.jpg"
    alt="Big Facist, Little Greg"><figcaption>
      <p>Here&rsquo;s a picture of Bovino letting the folks of Chicago know he&rsquo;s on top of being a Facist dick.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<h2 id="governmental-breakdown">Governmental Breakdown</h2>
<p>What has transpired since Agent Orange took office for a second time, is pretty phenominal. Not in a good way for the rank and file here in the U.S. More of a, societal upheaval as the rich get on with betraying the nation that allowed them to amass the fortunes they&rsquo;ve aquired and stashed.</p>
<h2 id="this-some-obvious-visible-greed">This some obvious, visible greed.</h2>
<p>Never in my life, have I seen the greedheads get with it like this. A bourgoning desire to not contribute in any meaningful way, to the environment that allowed freedom like no other. Grants, subsidies, bailouts. Nothing on the menu is too good for the Elite of America, eh? They continue to hoover up any and all available currency, with pennies on the dollar in return to society.</p>
<h2 id="christ-hang-on-for-the-ride">Christ&hellip; Hang on for the ride.</h2>
<p>Resist these swine. If we don&rsquo;t resist now, it&rsquo;ll be even harder to dislodge them, later on.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Shitass of the Week</title>
            <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitassoftheweek/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://shitass.life/home/posts/shitassoftheweek/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-shitass-parade&#34;&gt;The Shitass Parade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;week-of-jan-25th---31st&#34;&gt;Week of Jan 25th - 31st:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ICE Barbie Noem. Queen of the MAGA Prom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;K. Noem is seemingly, a horrid person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is now a known blatant liar, on air, easy peasy to catch her vile act;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Amhb8PK_an8&#34;&gt;Noem, Lying to the Nation&lt;/a&gt; about Alex Pretti being some kind of &amp;ldquo;terrorist&amp;rdquo;.
Does she hide behind trying to scare people? Oh yeah. Does she know absolutely nothing about the laws she is supposed to be dealing with? Hmmmmmm. If one listens to Noem attempting to answer serious questions, for any length of time, it&amp;rsquo;s apparant she&amp;rsquo;s lacking any serious study into the topics she tries to stumble through.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-shitass-parade">The Shitass Parade</h2>
<h2 id="week-of-jan-25th---31st">Week of Jan 25th - 31st:</h2>
<p>ICE Barbie Noem. Queen of the MAGA Prom.</p>
<p>K. Noem is seemingly, a horrid person.</p>
<p>She is now a known blatant liar, on air, easy peasy to catch her vile act;
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Amhb8PK_an8">Noem, Lying to the Nation</a> about Alex Pretti being some kind of &ldquo;terrorist&rdquo;.
Does she hide behind trying to scare people? Oh yeah. Does she know absolutely nothing about the laws she is supposed to be dealing with? Hmmmmmm. If one listens to Noem attempting to answer serious questions, for any length of time, it&rsquo;s apparant she&rsquo;s lacking any serious study into the topics she tries to stumble through.</p>
<p>Will she do anything for Donald Trump that serves her greed? Um, in my opinion, after her Pretti speech. She&rsquo;ll do anything it takes to accomplish what the orange dildo wants. The woman that Noem could have become, if not apparantly seducded by fuck-tons of cash and opportunity, could have been a powerful force for positive change in this nation.</p>
<p>I suppose it&rsquo;s easier to just say WTF, I need to get paid.</p>
<h4 id="cos-play-time-anyone-damn-if-she-aint-tacticool">Cos-Play Time Anyone? Damn if she ain&rsquo;t Tacticool!</h4>
<figure class="ma0 w-50"><img src="/static/iceBarbie.jpg"
    alt="ICE Barbie Queen"><figcaption>
      <p>Noem and Lewandowski sitting in a sty. Corey blew his wad, into Kristy&rsquo;s eye. She threw a fucking fit, and ran away, but Corey really runs the show on the day to day.</p>
    </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Yeah, that&rsquo;s one real winner.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>WTF Over?</title>
            <link>https://shitass.life/home/posts/wtfover/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://shitass.life/home/posts/wtfover/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-internet-has-not-been-your-friend&#34;&gt;The Internet, has not Been Your Friend.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here we are. Take a look around, it appears sorta sketchy and not friendly right now. The disinformation onion that is the Internet, has fucked the United States up, flatter than a hammered cock. How useful is a hammered cock people?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is it we always want to believe the worst about one another, without really looking at ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m left with assumptions, can&amp;rsquo;t answer the above other than to hazard, we forget to act and think from a place of love. The universe for humans, is governed by fear and love. We have to choose daily, how we are going to approach the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-internet-has-not-been-your-friend">The Internet, has not Been Your Friend.</h2>
<p>But here we are. Take a look around, it appears sorta sketchy and not friendly right now. The disinformation onion that is the Internet, has fucked the United States up, flatter than a hammered cock. How useful is a hammered cock people?</p>
<p>Why is it we always want to believe the worst about one another, without really looking at ourselves?</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m left with assumptions, can&rsquo;t answer the above other than to hazard, we forget to act and think from a place of love. The universe for humans, is governed by fear and love. We have to choose daily, how we are going to approach the world.</p>
<h2 id="flat-earth-and-q-critical-thinking-remains-deeply-unpopular">Flat Earth and Q; Critical Thinking Remains Deeply Unpopular.</h2>
<p>Before the prominance in our lives of the Internet, both Flat Earth and Q proponents would have been committed to an asylum or learned to keep shit on the down low.</p>
<p>The American penchant for contrarianism and anti-intellectualism has now been given the biggest microphone ever. That the Earth can be proven a globe is no matter to people who have decided, they know the truth bc of secret sources that, &rsquo;the they&rsquo;s&rsquo; don&rsquo;t want us to know about.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s ok that some people are smarter (or faster, stronger, Etc&hellip;) than us. Yo! It all leavens out. It does suck that things like, &ldquo;Nicotene has been shown to cause cancer.&rdquo; But it took smart people to figure it out for the rest of us, corporations were just going to keep taking adavntage of human addictive behavior and kill us early to make a buck.</p>
<p>Conversley though, smart motherfuckers shouldn&rsquo;t be just thinking all the rest of us are stupid. Again, it all leavens out and truely, we&rsquo;re all in it together.</p>
<h2 id="step-3-change">Step 3. Change.</h2>
<p>Sometimes, some change is needed, so things can run better. Change is required on all sides of the coin. Neither political party is worth a wet cotton sock in a snowstorm, as both are locked in thrall to corporate money and social networking likes.</p>
<p>There is a huge amount of money arrayed against meaningful change. In my opinion, unlimited money. The rich have decided were going back to the 1800&rsquo;s style of global carve up. What can I say about that other than, greed blinds folks from historical facts. I guess that when yer rich as Midas, you begin to believe that, you aren&rsquo;t subject to the same mistakes others have made before. Drunks call it, ten foot tall &rsquo;n bulletproof. Some philosophers would call it, an egoic lack of self honesty. I call it, morons with money.</p>
<p>We have to practice and get better at not taking their money for inaction. If anything, heh. We need to fool them into funding our action to corral their power and ability to wreak havoc on our lives.</p>
<h2 id="step-4-having-and-being-a-better-nation">Step 4. Having and being a better nation.</h2>
<p>Isn&rsquo;t having and holding something that lives up to the founding documents of the United States of America a worthy &rsquo;thinig&rsquo; in and of itself? I believe myself to be deeply American and was raised with the values of my Grandparents. The generation who so many look to through a nostolgic haze, the folks who held it down throughout the scrap w/ Imperial Japan and the Third Reich. What&rsquo;s funny is the grandparents who raised me, could look candidly at the past they had survived and agree that, &ldquo;The only good thing about the good old days is that they are gone.&rdquo; I mean it quite literally as well, they survived.
He (and a few hundred other souls) had a ship blown out from under him and sunk sitting at Lunga Roads, Ironbottom Sound, Solomon Islands. Then, after he and other shipless lads, formed Advanced Naval Base parties, to man the forward bases built by CB&rsquo;s. On Vella Lavella, while attempting to save some lads from NZ, he picked up a Silver Star and his second Purple Heart (single star).
She got Tuberculosis when my ma was a kid. Was put into a sanitarium w/ the other &rsquo;lungers&rsquo; (she told me that when I was 7, to my horror), so that he and my ma would go see her on weekends. For six months. They were tough as nails just because they had to be, when it was needed.
My dad&rsquo;s parents were slightly more conservative, but cast from the same mold of needing to be tough because of the times.</p>
<p>Not going to varnish over things, both sets of grandparents had some (to me, as a kid), astonishing racial views. That said however, they all were willing to modify beliefs as they got older. Not out of fear either, they all trusted people like my ma, who in a lot of ways, was a very progressive type, and introduced them to different people of different backgrounds.</p>
<p>The biggest catch to it all, those crafty grandparents of mine. They really meant it when they told me, &ldquo;It matters not what color, creed or original nationality. When someone is here and a, law-abiding, participating member of American society, they are welcome to the club.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 id="so">So.</h2>
<h3 id="go-fuck-yerself-stephen-miller-and-fuck-project2025-26">Go fuck yerself Stephen Miller, and fuck Project2025-26.</h3>
<p>Vought and Miller, sitting in a tree. One tried to screw, the crease in the others knee. First came hate, then came marraige, they push Trump around in a baby carraige.</p>
<p>Hideous rhymes aside, were in a pickle. The &rsquo;elites&rsquo; are seemingly trying to lock dissent out via their tools in D.C. and at the regional level. But it&rsquo;s financial as well. The push for the U.S. stablecoin looks to be enmeshed w/ the Trump family in too many ways to be good for anyone else. The family&rsquo;s past is the record to go off of, and it&rsquo;s corrupt. Seemingly, nothing they do is above board.</p>
<p>Note, not grandparent condoned language, but they&rsquo;d get it at this point in time. I knew them well enough, as they lived long lives and were in their late 40&rsquo;s when I was born. They hooked me up w/ some choice vocab. One of the sayings I&rsquo;m remembering most right now is; &ldquo;The fix is in.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Back with more scuttlebutt later on!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
