<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Outlaws on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/outlaws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outlaws on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/outlaws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shitass of the Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitassoftheweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shitassoftheweek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-shitass-parade&#34;&gt;The Shitass Parade&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;week-of-jan-25th---31st&#34;&gt;Week of Jan 25th - 31st:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ICE Barbie Noem. Queen of the MAGA Prom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;K. Noem is seemingly, a horrid person.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She is now a known blatant liar, on air, easy peasy to catch her vile act;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Amhb8PK_an8&#34;&gt;Noem, Lying to the Nation&lt;/a&gt; about Alex Pretti being some kind of &amp;ldquo;terrorist&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Does she hide behind trying to scare people? Oh yeah. Does she know absolutely nothing about the laws she is supposed to be dealing with? Hmmmmmm. If one listens to Noem attempting to answer serious questions, for any length of time, it&amp;rsquo;s apparant she&amp;rsquo;s lacking any serious study into the topics she tries to stumble through.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF Over?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wtfover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wtfover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-internet-has-not-been-your-friend&#34;&gt;The Internet, has not Been Your Friend.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But here we are. Take a look around, it appears sorta sketchy and not friendly right now. The disinformation onion that is the Internet, has fucked the United States up, flatter than a hammered cock. How useful is a hammered cock people?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why is it we always want to believe the worst about one another, without really looking at ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m left with assumptions, can&amp;rsquo;t answer the above other than to hazard, we forget to act and think from a place of love. The universe for humans, is governed by fear and love. We have to choose daily, how we are going to approach the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
